# **Dalton Drumm**

Drummd043@gmail • 626-629-9294 • 2125 S Redwood Ontario, CA 91762

## **Objective**

I have worked in the customer service field for eight years as an instructor, team leader and manager. With these skills I have developed and strengthened over the years, I am looking to take on new challenges in forming a new career path in the Web Development field.

### **Education & Certifications**

### California State University Long Beach

Cyber Security Professional Certificate Program

### University of California, Los Angeles

UCLA Extension, Full Stack Development Program

-MERN stack

-https://github.com/Drummd

Long Beach, CA

June 2020 - February 2021

June 2022 - current (Dec)

### **Projects**

## Movie Recommendation Generator: Flick Genie

Flick Genie is a movie generator that provides users with ideas of new movies to watch based on a movie they really enjoy at that time. This project was developed with single page applications with javascript coordinated with proper API pulls of the proper information.

Github-link: https://github.com/stang91/movie-recommendation-gen

# **Prophecy Generator:** Sage the Seer

Sage the Seer is a quote generator with a custom made database and API. This project utilized handlebars for the front end and prioritized proper routing control throughout the project. The User has the ability to sign in or sign up and go through a sequence of questions to be told their prophecy.

Github-link: https://github.com/Conklinj09/Sage-The-Seer

#### **Experience**

### **Mckinley Children Center**

Program Support Specialist

Oct 2019 - Sept 2022

As a Program support specialist for Mckinley I worked with K-12 kids with emotional disorders and special needs. My responsibilities as a (PSS) were based on crisis control and aversion with students in a aggressive or disruptive state of mind. I also helped the teachers when IEP's needed to be covered or certain kids needed to be tested. I opened the school and helped maintain a smooth transition for the

Los Angeles, CA

students coming into school and leaving the campus. I managed multiple 1 to 1's that provided support to students with particular needs from there districts and provided counselors to students when needed.

#### Hustler

Inventory Manager

Feb 2017 - Oct 2019

As Inventory Manager for Hustler, I streamlined and implemented an inventory system that corporate headquarters adopted and still uses today. Because of my accomplishment with creating the new inventory system, I had the sole responsibility of training other facilities managers and staff. My primary responsibilities included building daily, weekly and monthly inventory reports for regional managers, fulfilling online transactions and coordinated store to store shipments and inventory. I worked alongside the helpdesk to troubleshoot any technical issues with our computerized system.

#### **United Parcel Service**

Package Handler

Jan 2016 - Jan 2017

My primary responsibilities included loading and unloading parcels from delivery trunks and ensuring that our team met our supervisor's goals and delivery deadlines on time.

# **Target Corporation**

Cashier

Oct 2015 – Jan 2016

My responsibilities as a cashier for Target included but not limited to processing customer transactions, providing suggestive selling for Target Red Card members and assisted customers with inquiries about Target products and aided with cart retrieval.